<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[loganlinnlogs]]></title>
  <link href="http://loganlinn.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://loganlinn.com/"/>
  <updated>2011-12-26T19:37:16-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://loganlinn.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Logan Linn]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Running Octopress]]></title>
    <link href="http://loganlinn.com/blog/2011/10/15/now-running-octopress/"/>
    <updated>2011-10-15T16:12:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://loganlinn.com/blog/2011/10/15/now-running-octopress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As my friends are aware, I love <a href="http://ruby-lang.org">Ruby</a> [1]. I was,
and still am, hungry to write more of it.  Shortly after putting up my
<a href="http://loganlinn.heroku.com">wimpy Rails app for blogging</a>, I had
a feeling that it wasn&#8217;t going to work that well. I realized I mainly
wrote the app to create something in Rails and deploy it on Heroku. Fun,
but not a long term solution. I got discouraged and <s>stopped</s>
failed to start blogging in hopes to build a system I would use.</p>

<p>Still trying to feed my Ruby appetite, I decided to use Sinatra to make
a super simple app that would serve my static
<a href="http://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/">Markdown</a> files. But
somewhere in between graduating and moving across the country, I lost
track of that project and its source code. I also learned about
<a href="https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll">Jekyll</a>, which did everything I
wanted my app to do and more. I got discouraged again.</p>

<p>Today I learned about <a href="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</a>, a Sinatra
based framework that utilizes Jekyll. Described as an, &#8220;obsessively
designed framework&#8221;, I was delighted to find that it&#8217;s almost exactly
what I wanted to build myself. And since it&#8217;s a Rack app, it plays nice
with <a href="http://pow.cx/">pow</a>, another tool I&#8217;ve been looking for a reason
to use. So, shout out to <a href="https://github.com/imathis">Brandon Mathis</a>
and the Octopress contributors for making a great tool!</p>

<p>[1] They&#8217;ll also tell you that I have attention deficit disorder when it
comes to learning and using new programming languages.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[gitcrunch]]></title>
    <link href="http://loganlinn.com/blog/2011/05/03/gitcrunch/"/>
    <updated>2011-05-03T21:32:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://loganlinn.com/blog/2011/05/03/gitcrunch</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Just finished the last project for my Internet Software Development
course (VT&#8217;s CS4244). It compares the similarity between repositories
hosted on github. Repositories are scored based on similar commit
patterns. The two dimensions that are currently incorporated are hour
of the day and day of the week.</p>

<p>You can check out the project is at <a href="http://gitcrunch.com">http://gitcrunch.com</a>.</p>

<p><em>Update: This is now offline. I will try to resurrect the project
sometime.</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
